In this video, we will see, basically, we are going to enumerate few things, which we actually
need from the target computer, okay, so we already got our initial access.
We installed the cobalt sick payload through dealer injection, so I have installed multiple
scripts you can see here, okay, so I teach you how to do that.
So, let me interact with this, so before that, you can see only few options here.
Now you can see there is a lot of options we can use, there is an anti-farranted scale
and there is an enumeration key and persistence based key, there are a lot of options here.
So, if you want to kill any internal process, you can do that.
If you want to create a persistence, so you can do that and silver tickered, ad-based activity,
so you can, you can do that, okay, then we click on the interact.
So previously, we have enumerated the anti-verse things, right, so we have given a query
called AV query, here you can see, so Windows Defender version, this version, Windows Defender
for running under on the machine, okay, so you can do more if you want to go for a team
persistence, you can create a persistence and access, so if you need to go for a screenshot,
you can take a screenshot from this and if you want to go for a EDR query, let me, let
me get the IP here, so the IP address of this machine is 160.18.34.34, let us execute this,
so determining what EDR process has been installed, we will see the screenshots, so if
it has been available, so here you can see the screenshot of a Windows machine, so this is the
things which we have here, let me go to the Bcon and we will give a help command, so there
is few options in a help command process monitor, okay, so it will monitor all the process,
so red repo or a team based propose, so here, let me will give red repo, we will see
what are the files, inside the red repo, what are the options you can use in red repo,
let us see, see we have scanners, we have enumeration scutes, red can we can run, there
is a lot of options, we can go ahead and run with that, okay, get Firefox password, find
the key postconfig and invoke mini cats, let me invoke the mini cats, so this is based
on you, you can explore each and everything, you can generate a SMB based payloads from
here, and you can send it to the target, okay, you can go for a fact, payload name,
maybe C SMB, okay, and we can go for EXE, so it was saved under the opi decobalt stake
folder, we will go for opi decobalt stake SMB, stage payload, ball strike, SMB, what
the, stage payload file, SMB, stage payload, here we have the file, so also we can, so here
you can see, it is displaying few, we are format mini, mini kittens has been running on
the machine, we will see, we have one function, okay, upload function, we will see, we will
upload some files to the target, so we have already generated of the payload, right, SMB
decobalt, we will install that, here it is SMBp, open and it was sending the file, let
me check the directory, where we are, so sometime the cupboard cycle will be bit slow,
it will be take some time to, giving the rest cells, here you can find, we are working
on the pictures directory, so a period is uploading SMBp.exe, we will check whether the
payload has been uploaded, you can check by giving the DIR command here, shell DIR,
we have injector, some modules, so it was stopping to run the command, let me see the
help here, so what are the other ways we can take.
We check the hopsec command, so it was showing some hopsec cell commands as a error, the
shell has been able, but the son able to execute the command, it was blocked, but here
you can see it is already enabled, remove hopsec profile to run this command, so don't
worry, we know how to do that, let's keep that part, here you can find SMBp, we will execute
the SMBp, execute SMBp.exe, okay, okay, the same, it was giving the same error, the
hopsec profile running command, something, we will see other ways to execute, we check
whether we have a run command, sorry, SMBp.exe, okay, now the task will be gone, so run,
if we have a run command, execute a program on a target and return the output, let's
see what will happen, the code check has another important thing, so if you click on the
credentials, so it will listing all the credentials, so my username, it will listing
the username and passwords to the hashes, let's wait for some time, it will bring this
hopsec I think, it was creating a noisy thing, we will unload, okay, so there's another
decon, we have at the two, three, seven, two, there is one more decon has been there,
let's, we will see from which code does communicating, automatically log an activator, so
let's, we will type something, so I didn't, it didn't load out the scripts before, okay,
I was loading the things now, even I was checking, so what's happening here, let we will
see this, and see what the process is, so now it does the thing, we have removed the
computing, okay, it was communicating from the explorer.exe, okay, okay, there's a, SMB
play has been here, and vanilla gone, okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
it was, it was a listing the current running pit, and the AV heaps, if there's a AV or something
hooking, hooking has been there, so it will display the thing as a red, and rows of, it will
display as a green and explorer as a blue, so maybe we can, when we, when we inject any cell
codes, we will be injecting into explorer, explorer or villa gone, so there it was, showing
a blue format, that was working, and then the keystrokes that we will see, there's no keystrokes
as been there, the impersonator, let me check the privilege, it will be in the medium
relationally, shell, to my slash call, so we will execute this command, and we will hop
of this video, and we will continue our discussion in the next video, see you, yep, we'll
wait for this on the map, in any way it's a medium and a level, and it goes listing a medium
and a level, and just a sheet of the security identifier of the user, and this user has
a user was in a local account member of administering a group, we can elevate this privilege
by user access control by passing in a privilege installation section, let's swap of, let's
swap of files, we'll see you guys in the next video, bye bye.